const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Which position player is known as "1" on the baseball diamond?',
    answers: [
      'Pitcher',
      'Catcher',
      'Shortstop',
      'First Baseman',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pitcher'
  },


  {
    question: 'How many players play defense on a baseball diamond?',
    answers:[
      '10',
      '12',
      '9',
      '8',
    ],
    correctAnswer: '9'
 },


  {
    question: 'The DH hits instead of the __.',
    answers: [
      'Shortstop',
      'Pitcher',
      'Catcher',
      'Center Fielder',
   ],
    correctAnswer: 'Pitcher'
  },

{
  question: 'What is an error?',
  answers: [
    'Striking out',
    'Running out of the basepaths',
    'Making a mistake on defense',
    'Getting a single',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'Making a mistake on defense'
},

{
  question: 'What is a full count?',
  answers: ['3-0',
    '3-2',
    '2-2',
    '4-0',
  ],
  correctAnswer: '3-2'
},

{
  question: 'How many strikes does it take to make an out?',
  answers: [
    '0',
    '1',
    '2',
    '3',
  ],
  correctAnswer: '3'
},

{
  question: 'What do players use to hit the ball?',
  answers: [
    'glove',
    'bat',
    'hands',
    'head',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'bat'
},

{
  question: 'What are the different levels of major league baseball\'s farm system?',
  answers: [
  	'A, AA, AAA',
    'X, Y, Z',
    'A, B, C',
    'MLB, NHL, MBA, NFL',
  ],
  correctAnswer: 'A, AA, AAA'
},

{
  question: 'How long is a regular baseball game?',
  answers: [
    '10 innings',
    '9 innings',
    '15 innings',
    'until people get tired',
  ],
  correctAnswer: '9 innings'
},

{
  question: 'How many teams are in the major leagues?',
  answers: [
    '15',
    '20',
    '100',
    '30',
  ],
  correctAnswer: '30'
}

]
